BARTOSZ BAZINSKI

Founder, Chief Operations Officer at SentiOne

Summary

Software developer, entrepreneur, working on applying cutting-edge research to real world. Expert in information extraction from the internet. Since 2011 managing everything required to make SentiOne transform how companies listen to customers. 6 mln euro in funding and 80 best talents onboard so far, with customers like Procter&Gamble, Beiersdorf, Huawei, Microsoft, PwC and 500 other clients, we are destined to become the most insightful choice for social media listening and engagement.

Experience

Founder, Chief Operations Officer at SentiOne lipiec 2011 - Present

SentiOne is the leading social media monitoring company in Central and Eastern Europe. Our mission is to develop next-generation social listening platform. We help global and local brands track consumers opinions in social media and deliver valuable insights. We work with a few hundred cutting-edge marketing departments from companies like: Procter&Gamble, Unilever, Beiersdorf, Tesco, Starcom, Mindshare, Mediacom or Saatchi&Saatchi.

As the founder I am mainly responsible for the vision and technical side of the company.

Engineering team recruitment, planning and managing software development and deployment process, implementation of key algorithms, operational supervision of critical modules.

We started the company with 200k EUR in seed funding. Thanks to our great team we were profitable after 18 months. In 2016 we raised 3,5 mln EUR Series A funding to scale our business globally. Stay tuned!

Co-founder at ShareLook

czerwiec 2011 - czerwiec 2012 (1 rok 1 miesiąc)

Developed a proof-of-concept of mobile application for fashion recommendations, created strategy and business plan, acquired funding from seed fund.

CTO at EX3

czerwiec 2010 - czerwiec 2011 (1 rok 1 miesiąc)

EX3 was a software house doing web development projects fom customers from United Kingdom and Poland. I was responsible for the organization of the engineering teams, supervising projects specification and execution.

Lead Developer

luty 2007 - maj 2010 (3 lata 4 mies.)

Lead developer in several projects, mainly web extensions for ERP systems. Most interesting project was web system for registration of working time, developed for stock exchange listed construction company. Successfully deployed at over hundred remote construction sites, the system was collecting working records and calculating salaries for few thousands of employees.

Education

Politechnika Gdańska

Master of Science (MSc), Computer Science, 2007 - 2012 Activities and Societies: ICT Young 2011, ADBIS 2012

III LO Gdynia 2004 - 2007

Activities and Societies: Computer Science Olympiad, Robotics Club

Honors and Awards

V4 Startups & Scale-ups 2016 Winner, Microentrepreneur of the Year, Award for an outstanding Master Thesis, Scholarship in the Ventures programme, Winner of Robodance 2005, Winner of National Competition in Informatics

BARTOSZ BAZINSKI

Founder, Chief Operations Officer at SentiOne



Contact BARTOSZ on LinkedIn